TRACY HUBER

Tmhuber3@gmail.com ♦ 314-766-2324 ♦ https://github.com/megathuber

SUMMARY

My education began in accounting which has helped me to be extremely detail oriented with strong analytical skills and a true understanding of business financials. Additionally, I owned my own business for several years and for the past three years I have gained experience in the lending industry. My current sales role relies heavily on interpersonal communication skills. As a lifelong learner, I recently graduated from LaunchCode where I improved my skill set for today's technology driven environment.

EDUCATION

LaunchCode LC101 Python, SQL, HTML, CSS, Spring, IntelliJ IDE, Java, Github

UMSL CETC Intro to SQL and Intermediate Applications of SQL

NMLS Licensed Loan Officer Webster University BS in Accounting

EMPLOYMENT

Licensed Mortgage Advisor

Delmar Mortgage

2016-Present

- 3 years sales experience in a fast-paced and deadline-driven environment where I work primarily remote in a self-directed sales role
- Extensive planning and scheduling through Outlook, Excel and the CRM system for marketing campaigns and tracking loan progress milestones on current loan files
- Experience collaborating and working across teams to support all parties in a home purchase transaction
- Financial advising and debt planning experience as well as credit repair coaching with many clients
- Experienced speaker with home buying and debt planning seminars

Gym Manager

Xcel Gymnastics

2011-2016

- 5 years business management experience, including experience negotiating and documenting of contracts and agreements
- Managed policy structure to reduce organizational risk and align with business objectives
- Facility and operations management of a 15,000 square foot space in Chesterfield with 25+ employees and over 400 students
- Extensive experience in a customer facing environment
- Scheduled and coordinated various programs, class sessions, fundraising events, detailed marketing calendar, and outreach programs within the St. Louis community
- Extensive experience with Microsoft Office Suite and Rec1 online registration and database management system

Sales Coordinator

Industrial Battery Products

2008-2011

- Project management experience as part of our SAP implementation team
- Experience in operations and supply chain management working as sales coordinator in IBPs sister company Midwest Lumination
- Project management experience managing commercial lighting jobs from purchase to installation
- Regular face to face interaction with the customer base
- Collaborated and developed weekly PowerPoint Go-To Webinars for our regional sales team
- Experience in a fast paced, technical environment with detailed purchase orders and change orders for lighting installs